Guide to the Records of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute RG.21.35
New York University Archives
- Series VI: Media
  - DVCs
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable Healing and Nutritional Values, 2001 April 21; RG2135_86 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable Healing and Nutritional Values, 2001 April 21; RG2135_87 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable on Religious Ideologies, 2001 April 21; RG2135_88 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Roundtable on Religious Ideologies, 2001 April 21; RG2135_89 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow/Lecture/Tastings, 2001 April 21; RG2135_90 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Slideshow/Lecture/Tastings, 2001 April 21; RG2135_91 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Crossroads, 2001 April 21; RG2135_92 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--Southeast Asian Crossroads, 2001 April 21; RG2135_93 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--US Media and Southeast Asian Cuisine, 2001 April 21; RG2135_94 (Box 69)
    - Palates of Pleasure--US Media and Southeast Asian Cuisine, 2001 April 21; RG2135_95 (Box 69)
    - PDA Opening, 1998 November 12; RG2135_96 (Box 69)
    - PDA Opening, 1998 November 12; RG2135_97 (Box 69)
    - PDA After Party, 1998 November 14; RG2135_98 (Box 69)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 30; RG2135_99 (Box 69)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 19; RG2135_100 (Box 69)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 30; RG2135_101 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--Opening Remarks, 2000 March 31; RG2135_102 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Current State of Mental Health Services, RG2135_103 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Migration and Identity, RG2135_104 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Migration and Identity, RG2135_105 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Cross Cultural Clinical Practice, 2000 April 1; RG2135_106 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Match And Mismatch, RG2135_107 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference, RG2135_108 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Psychoanalytic Therapy, RG2135_109 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Psychoanalytic Therapy, RG2135_110 (Box 69)
    - Social Work Conference--On Cultural Competence Training, RG2135_111 (Box 69)
    - Suheir Hammad, 2001 February 21; RG2135_112 (Box 69)
    - Thuy Le Reading, 1999 October 28; RG2135_113 (Box 69)
    - Thuy Le Reading, 1999 October 28; RG2135_114 (Box 69)
    - Vestiges of War--Gamalinda, RG2135_115 (Box 69)
    - Vestiges of War--Body Count, RG2135_116 (Box 69)
    - Vestiges of War--Body Count, RG2135_118 (Box 69)
    - Vestiges of War--Body Count, RG2135_117 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Looking the Other Way, RG2135_119 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Looking the Other Way, RG2135_120 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Looking the Other Way, RG2135_121 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--The Object of Colonial Desire, RG2135_122 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--The Object of Colonial Desire, RG2135_123 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--The Object of Colonial Desire, RG2135_124 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Past Meets Present, RG2135_125 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Past Meets Present, RG2135_126 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Past Meets Present, RG2135_127 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Reception, 1999 February 19; RG2135_128 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--Reception, 1999 February 19; RG2135_129 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--View from the Diaspora, RG2135_130 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--View from the Diaspora, RG2135_131 (Box 70)
    - Vestiges of War--View from the Diaspora, RG2135_132 (Box 70)
    - Vijay Iyer and Kuni, 2003 April 3; RG2135_133 (Box 70)
    - Vijay Iyer and Kuni, 2003 April 3; RG2135_134 (Box 70)
    - Wilfredo Lam Question and Answer, 2002 November 6; RG2135_135 (Box 70)
    - Wilfredo Lam Question and Answer, 2002 November 6; RG2135_136 (Box 70)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; RG2135_137 (Box 70)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; RG2135_138 (Box 70)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; RG2135_139 (Box 70)
    - Youth Forum Meetings, 1999-2000; RG2135_140 (Box 70)
    - Youth Forum Meetings, 2000; RG2135_141 (Box 70)
    - Youth Forum Meetings, 2000; RG2135_142 (Box 70)
    - Youth Forum Youth Training, 2000; RG2135_143 (Box 70)
    - Youth Identity Forum--Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 April 7; RG2135_144 (Box 70)
    - Youth Identity Forum--Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 April 7; RG2135_145 (Box 70)
    - Youth Identity Forum--Exploring the Unseen and Unspoken, 2000 April 7; RG2135_146 (Box 70)
    - Youth Identity Forum, 1999 March 5; RG2135_147 (Box 70)
    - Race and Social Justice: Diallo Verdict, March 2000; RG2135_148 (Box 70)
    - Race and Social Justice: Diallo Verdict, March 2000; RG2135_149 (Box 70)
    - Race and Social Justice: Diallo Verdict, March 2000; RG2135_150 (Box 70)
  - CD
    - AWU at NYU, 2004 September 25; cuid474 (Box 19)
    - Jamez, cuid475 (Box 19)
    - APAYA, 2001-2006; cuid477 (Box 19)
    - Workshops, cuid478 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Tshirt, 2005; cuid479 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Logo, 2005; cuid480 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Logo, cuid481 (Box 19)
  - VHS
    - 50 Yen "Changsta", cuid18595 (Box 19)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, 1998 December 12; cuid482 (Box 18)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, 1998 December 12; cuid483 (Box 18)
    - ACEH Indonesia Conference, 1998 December 12; cuid484 (Box 18)
    - APAYA Skits, 2001-2003; cuid18594 (Box 19)
    - APAYA Trailer, cuid485 (Box 18)
    - Artist in Residence Kickoff Celebration, 2004; cuid486 (Box 18)
    - Asians in America--NYU Equal, 1996; cuid487 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference, 1997; cuid488 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference, 1997; cuid489 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference Phil Nash, 1997; cuid490 (Box 18)
    - Asian American Conference Phil Nash, 1997; cuid491 (Box 18)
    - Asian Women United Reunion, 2004 September 25; cuid492 (Box 18, Vhs cuid492)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Duration: 84 min, Color, Sound
    - Breaking Stereotypes--APA Musicians, 2003 April 3; cuid493 (Box 18)
    - Brown Bag Lunch Series with John Kuo Wei Tchen--Revisioning the City, cuid494 (Box 18)
    - Chang Rae Lee Reading, 2000 April 11; cuid495 (Box 18)
    - Civil Rights Issues and Post 9-11, 2003 May 21; cuid496 (Box 18)
    - Corky Lee Artist Talk, 2003 March 4; cuid497 (Box 18, Vhs cuid497)
    - Corky Lee and Mel Rosenthal's Two Men, Two Cameras, Different Perspectives, 2002 December 5; cuid498 (Box 18, Vhs cuid498)
    - Dale Minami Lecture, 2003 September 22; cuid499 (Box 18)
    - Dangerous Music, Fierce Women Reading, 1998 October 29; cuid500 (Box 18, Vhs cuid500)
    - Dogeaters from Novel to Stage, 2001 January 30; cuid501 (Box 18)
    - Dogeaters from Novel to Stage, 2001 January 30; cuid502 (Box 18)
    - Emerging Artists--Stacy Ann Chin's I Was Born With Two Tongues, 1999 November 17; cuid503 (Box 18)
    - Emerging Artists--Stacy Ann Chin's I Was Born With Two Tongues, 1999 November 17; cuid504 (Box 18)
    - Fay Chiang Artist in Residence, 2003-2004; cuid505 (Box 18)
    - Flower Drum Song on NYU Tonight and CNN Student Bureau, cuid506 (Box 18)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Symposium, 2002 October 11; cuid507 (Box 18)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Annual Asian/Pacifics in America Conference, 2002 October 12; cuid508 (Box 18)
    - Flower Drum Song Camera, cuid509 (Box 18)
    - Flower Drum Song Camera, cuid510 (Box 18)
    - Jaishri Abichandani Meet the Artist, 2002 June 12; cuid511 (Box 18)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, 1998 September 23; cuid512 (Box 18)
    - Maya Lin and Michael Brenson Dialogue, 1998 September 23; cuid513 (Box 18)
    - Nobuko in A Grain Of Sand, 1995 June 9-25; cuid514 (Box 18)
    - Rethinking NYC, 2002 October 30; cuid515 (Box 18)
    - Sia Figiel Reading, 2000 April 13; cuid516 (Box 18)
    - Third World Newsreel, cuid517 (Box 18)
    - Third World Newsreel, cuid518 (Box 18)
    - Third World Newsreel, cuid519 (Box 18)
    - Two Bells, Two Worlds Film Screening and Discussion, 2003 October 4; cuid520 (Box 18)
    - Wen Ho Lee, 2002 February 13; cuid521 (Box 18)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond, 2003 April 23; cuid522 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond, 2003 April 23; cuid523 (Box 19)
    - You Are Being Watched, 2003 February 7; 2018-02; cuid524 (Box 19, Vhs cuid524, Box Shared University Archives 118, Item 29)
      Duration: 133 min.
    - Youth Forum Training, 2000 March 25; cuid525 (Box 19)
  - DVCAM
    - Flower Drum Song--A Roundtable Discussion, 2002 October 6; cuid526 (Box 19)
    - Flower Drum Song--With C.Y. Lee Interview, 2002 October 6; cuid527 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid528 (Box 19)
    - Wen Ho Lee's My Country Versus Me, 2002 April 1; cuid529 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid530 (Box 19)
  - Floppy Disk
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid531 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid532 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid533 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid534 (Box 19)
    - Asians in America, 1997; cuid535 (Box 19)
    - Japanese American National--Images for America's Concentration Camps, cuid536 (Box 19)
    - White House Initiative on AAPIs and FreeZone Symposium, cuid537 (Box 19)
    - APAYA, cuid538 (Box 19)
    - APAYA 01 Group Picture, Circa 2001-2002; cuid539 (Box 19)
    - APAYA 01 Nchink, Circa 2001-2002; cuid540 (Box 19)
    - Unlabeled 1 of 2, Undated; cuid541 (Box 19)
    - Unlabeled 2 of 2, Undated; cuid542 (Box 19)
  - DAT
    - Raising Our Voices, 2002 September 19; cuid543 (Box 66)
  - Hi8 ProMP
    - Asians in America--Poetics of Politics and Sex, 1999; cuid544 (Box 66)
    - Asians in America--Representant Blues, 1999; cuid545 (Box 66)
    - Asians in America--Conversations with Elaine Kim, 1999; cuid546 (Box 66)
    - Asians in America--Is The Book Dead?, 1999; cuid547 (Box 66)
    - Asians in America--Book Reading, 1999; cuid548 (Box 66)
  - DVD-R
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond A/P/A Panel, cuid549 (Box 19)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond A/P/A Panel, cuid550 (Box 19)
  - Cassettes
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid551 (Box 66)
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid552 (Box 66)
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid553 (Box 66)
    - ACEH Indonesia, 1998 December 12; cuid554 (Box 66)
    - Albert Chong Works in Progress, cuid555 (Box 66)
    - Ancestors in the Americas Film Screening and Discussion, cuid556 (Box 66)
    - APA Studies Conference, 2004 April 16; cuid557 (Box 66)
    - APA Studies Conference, 2004 April 16; cuid558 (Box 66)
    - APA Studies Conference, 2004 April 16; cuid559 (Box 66)
    - Artists and History Making, cuid560 (Box 66)
    - The Atlantic World, 1997 October 11; cuid561 (Box 66)
    - Awards Ceremony, cuid562 (Box 66)
    - Backstage Pass Session III of Hidden Histories of Popular Music, cuid563 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid564 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid565 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid566 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid567 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid568 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid569 (Box 66)
    - Civil Rights Issues, 2003 May 21; cuid570 (Box 66)
    - Community Activism, cuid571 (Box 66)
    - Community Activism, cuid572 (Box 66)
    - Concrete Cultures Session I of Asian American Urban Practices, cuid573 (Box 66)
    - David Henry Hwang 20 Year Retrospective, 2000 November 14; cuid574 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid575 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid576 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid577 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid578 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid579 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid580 (Box 66)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid581 (Box 67)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid582 (Box 67)
    - Defining Communities of Interest--Citizenship, 2000 December 3; cuid583 (Box 67)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid584 (Box 67)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid585 (Box 67)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid586 (Box 67)
    - Diaspora U.S., cuid587 (Box 67)
    - Digital Dialogues: Asian-American Technoculture Practices, cuid588 (Box 67)
    - Freezone- Opening Remarks and Youth Cultures, 2000; cuid589 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Youth Cultures, 2000; cuid590 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Open Mic, 2000; cuid591 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Representation/Presentation, 2000; cuid592 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Situation Resolution and Creating Safe Spaces, 2000; cuid593 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Addressing the Needs of Youth, 2000; cuid594 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Youth Organizing, 2000; cuid595 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Asian Youth Culture, 2000; cuid596 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Panel, 2000; cuid597 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Current Issues, 2000; cuid598 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Community Involvement, 2000; cuid599 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Expressive Cultures, 2000; cuid600 (Box 67)
    - Freezone--Closing Symposium Reflections and Conclusions, 2000; cuid601 (Box 67)
    - Fictions of Asian America, 2004 April 17; cuid602 (Box 67)
    - Fictions of Asian America, 2004 April 17; cuid603 (Box 67)
    - Fictions of Asian America, 2004 April 17; cuid604 (Box 67)
    - Fluid Cultures, cuid605 (Box 67)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid606 (Box 67)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid607 (Box 67)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid608 (Box 67)
    - Gender, Cultural Citizenship, and Transnationalism Panel, cuid609 (Box 67)
    - Gender and Politics, cuid610 (Box 67)
    - Getting the Story Told, cuid611 (Box 67)
    - The Good Life Session I of Politics of Consumption, Pleasure, and Desire, cuid612 (Box 67)
    - History, Memory, Community, cuid613 (Box 67)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid614 (Box 67)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid615 (Box 67)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid616 (Box 67)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid617 (Box 67)
    - In The Country Of My Imagination, 2002 April 13; cuid618 (Box 67)
    - The John Huang Affair and Political Participation, cuid619 (Box 68)
    - Making History: New Settlements in the Americas, cuid620 (Box 68)
    - Magdalen Hsu-Li: Evolution National Tour, 1999; cuid621 (Box 68)
    - New Media and Community Building Roundtable, cuid622 (Box 68)
    - New Media and Community Building Roundtable, cuid623 (Box 68)
    - New Research/New Interpretation, cuid624 (Box 68)
    - Notes from the Asian Underground, cuid625 (Box 68)
    - Pan in Focus/Despers USA, cuid626 (Box 68)
    - Paradigm 2, The Americas, cuid627 (Box 68)
    - Program, 1998 November 13; cuid628 (Box 68)
    - The Real Deal? Asian American Cultural Politics, cuid629 (Box 68)
    - Reclaiming the Self/Reclaiming the History, cuid630 (Box 68)
    - Recovering Lives/Communities, cuid631 (Box 68)
    - Relocating: Enclaves Past, Present, and Future, cuid632 (Box 68)
    - Resident Aliens Session III of Cultural Citizenship and Pop Culture, cuid633 (Box 68)
    - Resources for Family History Preservation Workshop, cuid634 (Box 68)
    - Tape 1, cuid635 (Box 68)
    - To Wong Foo--The Migration of Popular Culture, cuid636 (Box 68)
    - Touring Chinatown--Problems and Possibilities, cuid637 (Box 68)
    - Touring Chinatown--Problems and Possibilities, cuid638 (Box 68)
    - Trinh Minh Ha Lecture, 2001 March 21; cuid639 (Box 68)
    - Vijay Iyer, 2000 February 23; cuid640 (Box 68)
    - Vijay Iyer Discussion, 2000 February 23; cuid641 (Box 68)
    - Where is Home for Asian-American Writers, cuid642 (Box 68)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid643 (Box 68)
    - Who's Next? North Korea and Beyond Teach In, cuid644 (Box 68)
    - Winifred Chin Paper Son Talk, 2003 April 14; cuid645 (Box 68)
  - Archived Websites, April 2014-March 2019; 3 websites in 3 archived websites.
    The Yellow Peril! project was a collaborative blog and website with intention to preserve and recontextualize artifacts from the history of anti-Asian fear in the United States, Europe, and other white dominated cultures. The website was maintained by John Kuo Wei Tchen and Mark Tseng Putterman. It contains Tchen's curriculum for Yellow Peril class; images of digitized artifacts that perpetuate anti-Asian sentiment in Fales and Tamiment collections; and commentaries on Islamophobia, transnational adoption, and other stereotyping of Asians in media. The website was active in 2014-2015. Also includes a rendering of the homepage and a sample page of the website.
    Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
    Appraisal
    Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored.
- Series VII: Artifacts
  Series VII contains a large A/P/A banner.
  - Banner, Undated (Box 21)